iibf.org.in 2014-12-03

# Welcome to Indian Institute of Banking & Finance

Privacy Policy  
---  
   
Data : The information that we gather from you is protected responsibly, keeping your privacy in mind. We do this by implementing the following measures.   
Security : Your personal information is stored in limited access servers.   
Registration Information : In order to register for iibf.org.in, you are asked to provide details such as your name and email address, title and organization. You will be able to review and change profile information by contacting the administrator directly : iibgen@bom5.vsnl.net.in.   
Use of Information : iibf.org.in uses this information to notify you of new features and custom-design content and advertising for registered users.   
The Sharing of Information : iibf.org.in may share information when legally required.   
Advertisers/Third Parties : These groups will have access to aggregate information. iibf.org.in will restrict any third parties from using registered user's information for purposes other than those to serve you. We furnish information to third parties only when they have a contractual agreement with iibf.org.in, binding them to the privacy standards of iibf.org.in [For a more specific description of the different ways our information may be used, contact Administrator via email].   
Links to Other Web Sites : This Privacy Policy does not pertain to Web sites other than iib.org.in If you link to another Web site from iibf.org.in, please consult that site’s privacy policy.   
Surveys : At times we may conduct surveys on the site. Participation is entirely voluntary. Your responses will be aggregated and anonymous.   
For more information on our Privacy Policy, contact Customer Service.   
iibf.org.in  
World Trade Center,  
'The Arcade', Cuffe Parade,  
Mumbai - 400 005.   
Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted accordingly. This policy was last updated on February 28, 2001.
